You I know.
Tuco's man.
He's okay.
Tuco's man?
Don Hector had a stroke.
We don't know when he will be back.
But listen to me...
Salamanca territory...
Stays salamanca territory.
Nothing changes.
Collections continue as before.
The count must be exact.
Anyone crosses a line...
You stop them.
You have a delivery tomorrow night.
You pick up, you package...
You distribute.
All as you've done before.
Do you understand?
You do this right...
Things could go very well for you.
The old bastard,
he's always been trouble.
But he keeps his house in order.
What do you think?
Someone will move
against the salamancas.
Which brings war.
Which brings chaos.
Which brings...
The d.E.A.