J“ we three, we're all alone j“
j“ living in a memory j“
j“ my echo, my shadow, and me j“
j“ we three
we 're not a crowd j“
j“ we 're not even company j“
j“ my echo, my shadow, and me j“
gene.
J“ what good is the moonlight
the silvery moonlight j“
man: What happened?
J“ I walk with my shadow j“
j“ I talk with my echo
but where is the one I love j“
j“ we three, we'll wait for you j“
j“ even till eternity j“
j“ my echo, my shadow and me j“
J“ we three, we're all alone j“
technician:
Light as you can. Take a deep breath.
J“ my shadow and me j“
J“ we three, we ain't no crowd j“
J“ that's my echo j“
j“ my shadow, and me j“
doctor: Mr. Takavic.
How you feeling?
Good. Yes.
It's good news. You're right.
It's not a heart attack.
In fact, everything I can
see here looks good.
Blood pressure's high...
But that's understandable
under the circumstances.
The headline is false alarm.
J“ and me j“j“
Mr. Takavic, sir?
I'm so sorry. Would you mind?
- I have a taxi coming.
- It'll just take a moment.
Could I have another look
at your driver's licence?
For some reason,
this computer keeps kicking this back.
- And this is your current address?
- Mm-hm.
Can I have your
social security number again?
Five, three, one...
That's the pacific northwest, right?
- Yeah.
- I got a cousin who moved to Tacoma.
It's supposed to be beautiful up there.
Yeah, it's...
Beautiful.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You got a taxi.
Go ahead. Five, three, one...
Oh, oh, eight...
Seven...
One...
Four.
Okay. That's five, three, one,
oh, oh, eight, seven, one, four?
That's really...
I've never seen this before.
Oh, wait.
Oh, my god.
I typed the letter o instead of a zero.
Ha-ha.
I can't believe how stupid...
I think it's...
Yeah, it's going through now.
So it's okay?
I'm so sorry.
- So I can...?
- Have a good night.
I'm sorry for keeping you.
Oh, hold on.
Don't forget this.
- Stay warm.
- You too.
Cottonwood mall, please.
It's... it's a green light.
Uh, you know what,
I'll just get out here.
Excuse me. This is good.
I'll get out here.
Great. Thanks.
Jimmy: Hey.
I'll trade you.
Let it go. If it's important,
they'll leave a message.
Kim: You've reached
Kim wexler. Please leave a message.
Uh, Kim, it's Howard.
I'm trying to reach Jimmy.
If you would please let him know.
I really need to talk to him.
It's Chuck.
Man: Everyone, clear.
Jimmy, don't.
- Thank you, Howard.
- Yes.
He says it started in the living room.
Somehow, one of the lanterns
was knocked over.
The inspector says it was over fast.
Smoke inhalation, so he didn't suffer.
Yeah, they're gonna say that.
Did you see the backyard?
His microwave...
His stereo, his, uh, lights...
Dishwasher, all the kitchen stuff...
Everything electric is back there.
The firemen didn't do that.
He did that.
I saw him five days ago.
He was listening to jazz.
All the lights worked.
He was himself.
Something must've happened.
Something made him relapse.
I think we should go home, Jimmy.
Okay?
Come on.
Let's just go home.
- Hey, Carl.
- Hey, Mike.
- There you go.
- So this is it, huh?
Looks that way.
You take it easy.
So the boss said
he's gonna want the windbreaker.
Of course he does.
Take care, Mike.
Make it go.
What's wrong with it?
You're standing on it.
Look down. You're standing on it.
Really?
Hey. Mike: Hey.
- Heh.
- You two having fun?
- Five more minutes, please?
- Five more minutes, but that's it.
- Hey, baby.
- Thank you.
Is that the soaker hose you two made?
Yeah. I can pick her up
the rest of the week if you want.
- You sure? What about your new job?
- I make my own hours.
Must be nice.
- Well, since you're offering...
- Good.
Thanks, Mike.
Man:
For the isotopes capturing the title.
The pitch on the outside, a cold strike.
Two and one to the right-hand-batting
McDonald, he doesn't agree.
Turns back to
the home plate umpire, tichenor.
Keith McDonald, last year,
played for Iowa.
And there, defore was a longtime
member of Memphis.
One for seven in the new campaign.
Right-hand batter with an open stance.
Hitting with the lead-off man. Nobody
out in a one-nothing game. The pitch.
Swing and a bouncer
through the right side. A base hit.
On the way to second is truby.
He 'i/ stop there. Pageant placed at bat.
Chris truby had to hurdle the baseball
on its way through the infield.
Otherwise, perhaps, he might've had
a chance to take the turn at second.
Already with back-to-back singles
and another threat in the works.
Las cruces for madrigal intermodal.
M—a-d-r-i-g—a—I.
In all six of their games now,
that they have not taken the first...
And would you have
an address for that?
Jimmy?
It's Howard.
I think you should talk to him.
Howard.
Howard: Jimmy, I'm so sorry
to bother you with this.
The thing is, we wanted to get Chuck's
obituary in the paper before the service.
But I'd really like to run it
by you if that's okay.
Yeah, go ahead.
Great.
Okay. "Charles Lindbergh mcgill.
A towering figure
in the Albuquerque legal community...
Who built one of the leading
law firms in the southwest...
Was taken from this world
tragically and suddenly last week.
Son of Ruth and Willard mcgill...
Charles was born and raised
in Cicero, Illinois, outside Chicago.
Charles graduated valedictorian from
Francis Xavier high school at 14...
Making him the youngest graduate
in the history of that school.
In his undergraduate years
at the university of Pennsylvania...
He led the debate team
to national championship...
Three years running
and won the Larkin prize.
He was editor-in-chief of the law review
and won the moot court competition...
At Georgetown law, where he went
on to graduate magna cum laude.
After clerking at
the Delaware court of chancery...
And the United States court
of appeals for the tenth circuit...
Charles joined
George Hamlin's solo practise...
On central Avenue
in downtown Albuquerque.
Over 23 years, the two men
built what became known...
As Hamlin Hamlin mcgill
into a nationally-recognised firm.
Charles made his Mark
in many areas of the law.
Early in his career,
he excelled in criminal law...
Winning the precedent-setting case
of state...
No matter the case,
Charles was known for his precise...
Clear arguments and his devotion
to the highest ideals of the law.
Charles was also active in the
community, championing education...
For the underserved.
He was on the boards of new Mexico
charities and a founding member of...
Southwestern coalition for better
schools and native education alliance.
Charles is survived by his former wife,
concert violinist Rebecca bois...
And his younger brother,
James mcgill...
Who followed in Charles' footsteps
and entered the legal profession."
And then there's information about the
memorial service. Date, time and all that.
So that is what I have.
- Jimmy?
- It's me, Howard. Sounds good.
- Oh. Jimmy's okay with it?
- He likes it, Howard. Go ahead with it.
Well...
All right.
Thank him for me.
And if you need anything...
- Let me know.
- Yeah, I will.
- See you Sunday.
- Yeah, see you Sunday.
Man:
Be advised. We have one adult male...
Woman: Does he have a history
of cardiac issues?
Nacho: Yeah.
Woman:
And was he taking any medications?
Nacho: He took these.
Woman: Thanks. We're headed
to lovelace if you'd like to follow.
Don Juan.
Juan bolsa wants to see you.
You drive.
You I know.
Tuco's man.
He's okay.
Tuco's man?
Ignacio.
Don Hector had a stroke.
We don't know when he will be back.
But listen to me...
Salamanca territory...
Stays salamanca territory.
Nothing changes.
Collections continue as before.
The count must be exact.
Anyone crosses a line...
You stop them.
You have a delivery tomorrow night.
You pick up, you package...
You distribute.
All as you've done before.
Do you understand?
You do this right...
Things could go very well for you.
The old bastard,
he's always been trouble.
But he keeps his house in order.
Gustavo.
What do you think?
Someone will move
against the salamancas.
Which brings war.
Which brings chaos.
Which brings...
The DEA.
What's up?
It's busted again.
It's just the chain.
Want me to do it
or you wanna try it yourself?
Okay.
This is the last time, so watch.
All right.
So you take this, give it a little play,
right about there.
Loop it around the big gear, yeah?
- That's all there is to it.
- Okay.
- And?
- Thanks, dad.
Make sure mom knows where you are.
Hi, Denise.
Uh, yeah, it's Barry.
Uh, listen, could you let Mr. Eglin know
I'm gonna be late this morning?
I might miss the staff meeting.
No, no. Car troubles.
Probably just a dead battery.
Yeah, I know. I know.
Practically brand-new.
Okay, thanks.
Bruce had the speed. He could
kick you before you saw him move.
- You ever watched a liston fight?
- We're talking about what?
- Boxing? That's something else.
- No, we're talking a street fight.
- Street fight? Great, so Bruce can kick.
- We're not talking a movie fight.
- We're talking about weight, about reach.
- Boxing is a sport.
Martial arts is life and death.
Look, I don't care how fast you are.
Muhammad Ali hits you,
you're going down, that's a fact.
If he hits you.
Bruce Lee, he knows the anatomy.
He's got the moves.
He's gonna find an opening.
Without power,
the opening doesn't mean squat.
- How much does he weigh?
- Man 1: Don't know. Maybe a buck-thirty.
Man 2: Ali was the heavyweight champ.
He's got a hundred pounds on Lee.
Man 1:
Bruce feints for Ali's head.
But he goes low and sweeps him
to the deck. Ali goes down hard.
It's all over.
Does he have a gun?
- I'm sorry?
- Does Bruce Lee have a gun?
If he doesn't,
it's Ali in three minutes or less.
See? That's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm say...
Hey, hold on. Wait, wait.
Did you sign, uh, Tina's birthday card?
- No.
- Would you mind?
Man 1: You're out of line.
Man 2: I'm saying...
If Lee tried to sweep Ali's legs,
he'll sidestep.
Ali was fast for his size, yes.
But if he gets hit with a low kick,
he won't know what to do.
Man 2:
I know what he'll do. He'll do just fine.
Man 1: You're nuts.
Bruce was a brawler, okay?
He gets in quick...
I got it.
Uh, yeah?
Ramirez, team leader.
Ramirez: Yes, sir.
Ramirez, what do you
think you're up to?
We're just pulling an order.
Something wrong?
May I ask why none of your guys
are wearing a lift belt?
Lift belt?
- We don't usually...
- Stop what you're doing.
Go to the equipment room.
You get lift belts and gloves.
You use them.
Rules are rules, got me?
Sure. Sure. Okay.
On the double.
Ramirez:
Hey, hold up. Shut it down.
Shut it down.
Uh, excuse me.
I think this belongs to you.
Oh, my god. Ha, ha.
Thank you. Where did you find it?
I need to talk to your manager.
I waltz through security
with someone else's ID.
Nobody gives me a second look.
When the rightful owner shows up,
there's no facility-wide badge check.
I find access doors left unlocked
or propped open.
Passwords written on post-it notes.
Warehouse workers are using pen and
paper instead of electronic devices...
Which leaves you open to pilfering.
You got duplicate
routing numbers on cargo.
Surveillance camera blind spots on
the north and the east side of the floor.
Inventory documents going into
the trash instead of being shredded.
Not to mention loading equipment
driven at unsafe speeds...
- Wait. Wait.
- And crews...
- Wait, hold on. Who are you exactly?
- Disregarding safe...
Ehrmantraut.
Security consultant.
Well, all due respect, I don't know
anything about a security consultant.
Well, you wouldn't, would you?
Maybe you'd best call corporate.
Try Lydia rodarte-ouayle.
Cliff: I'm truly sorry, Jimmy.
Thank you, cliff. I appreciate that.
Hey.
He was a hell of a lawyer.
Yes, he was.
Jimmy.
We're gonna miss him so much.
Thank you, Brenda.
- Brian: I'm sorry for your loss.
- Thanks, Brian.
Man: Jimmy, I'm so sorry.
Oh, thanks. Appreciate that.
Thank you.
I think I owe you the truth about Chuck.
Those lanterns.
He was living in that house
without electricity for two years.
He knew how to use those lanterns.
He was careful. I saw it. I know you
did too. There was never a problem.
I know it's a terrible thing to...
I don't think what happened
was an accident.
You probably heard
Chuck was retiring from hhm.
But that's not the truth.
The truth is that
we had a disagreement...
And I pushed him out.
I made him go.
Chuck was sick for years.
And after the bar hearing...
The bar hearing
had nothing to do with it.
Okay.
The fact is,
he started getting better after that.
He took more of an interest in the firm.
He came to work. We left the lights on.
He was improving until the thing with
the insurance, it wasn't the bar hearing.
The insurance?
It was a ridiculous thing.
I should've just let it go.
I mean, god knows
he's done enough for me.
But he kept pushing and I, um...
I got my back up.
What about the insurance?
Howard:
It was, uh, our malpractice insurance.
They found out about
Chuck's condition, raised our rates.
Chuck went ballistic.
He wanted to go to war.
I drew a line.
He wouldn't back down.
So I forced him out.
It never occurred to me
that I could hurt him.
He always seemed so strong.
But he wasn't.
I think he did what he did
because of me.
Well, Howard,
I guess that's your cross to bear.
Look at her go.
So I'm gonna make coffee.
Anybody want some?